Horse girls,
賽馬娘
girls who were born to race.
她們是為了奔跑而生的女孩
Some had a rocky fate.
有時因為其乖舛命運
Some left behind a legacy. In this wondrous world,
有時是與其擁有其光輝歷史的 異世界之名而誕生
they continued their journey via racing.
並繼承其靈魂而奔跑
That is their destiny.
那將是她們的命運
The race toward the best
誕生於這個世上的賽馬娘 她們的比賽結果
is still unfinished.
現在還無人知曉
So they run
她們將會繼續奔跑
and run
奔向在她們的眼前的
toward the finishing line.
那條終點線
The horse girls are heading into the third bend.
好的 各賽馬娘 從正面衝進第三彎道
Who will win the triple crown of Satsuki Sho?
到底誰能贏下這座 經典三冠的皐月賞呢
Me. It's going to be me.
要贏 我絕對要贏
I have never lost once.
我未曾一敗地拼到了這裡
I will win Satsuki Sho like Tokai Teio did.
我要像帝皇那樣贏下皐月賞
The popular Satono Crown is following closely behind.
在這時人氣選手里見皇冠衝了上來
Will we witness the birth of the long-awaited Satsuki Sho champion?
是會誕生 久違的無敗皐月賞賽馬娘呢
Will Satono Crown accomplish her family's wish?
還是里見家的夙願 會以這種形式來完成呢
Duramente!
是大鳴大放
She changed outward.
用像是被彈開的力道 從外側衝了出來
This is the final stretch. Other athletes are closing in.
進入了最終直線 後方的對手也追了上來
But the inside line is occupied by the leading athletes.
但是內線被領先選手所佔住
Satono Crown is in the middle of the pack.
里見皇冠還在中段位置
Can she close the gap?
她能夠追上來嗎
The final stretch isn't a long one.
中山的直線可是很短的
In the final stretch, Gentsu Steel appeared!
在進入最後直接時 玄津鋼鐵追上來了
200 meters left.
剩下200公尺
Kitasan Black is accelerating.
北部玄駒在內線不斷加速
Kitasan Black!
北部玄駒
-I have to win this. -Kitasan Black is in the inside line.
-要贏 我一定要贏 -裡面有北部玄駒 外面是玄津鋼鐵
Can she overtake Kitasan Black? She did!
她能超越北部玄駒嗎 超越了
Gentsu Steel is taking a small lead.
玄津鋼鐵些微領先
Duramente appears on the side.
大鳴大放從外側追上來了
Duramente! Can you believe it?
在外側的居然是大鳴大放
She's so fast.
她居然強成這樣嗎
Has she always been this strong?
實力居然如此驚人嗎
Duramente!
大鳴大放
Astounding!
厲害
Duramente won Satsuki Sho.
贏下皐月賞的是大鳴大放
Is this
這是上天所賜予的天生資質嗎
-Yes! -what you call
-好啊 -這是上天所賜予的天生資質嗎
a god-given talent?
這是上天所賜予的天生資質嗎
I can't believe it!
太可怕了
I…
我…
I lost.
我輸掉了
EPISODE 1: THE LINE IN SIGHT
(第1話 憧憬的景色)
TOKAI TEIO CAN TEIO SURPASS THE EMPEROR?
(東海帝皇) (帝王能超越皇帝嗎)
KITASAN BLACK
(北部玄駒)
Morning, Kita.
早安啊 小北
Morning, Diamond.
早安啊 光鑽
You're up early today. Be safe.
今天也很早起呢 要小心喔
I will.
好
See you then.
那我出發了
See you.
路上小心
SATONO DIAMOND
(里見光鑽)
Satsuki Sho,
皐月賞
my first G1
是我的第一場GI
and my first defeat.
也是我的第一場敗仗
Everyone is very strong there.
所有對手都很強勁
And the pressure is through the roof.
四周的空氣都很緊張
The next race will be the Japanese Derby.
但是下一場比賽是日本德比
The race everyone looks forward to.
是大家所憧憬的德比
I will race like the ever-awesome Teio.
我要像帥氣奔跑的帝皇那樣
Teio…
帝皇…
All right.
好
Here I come!
北部玄駒 要衝刺了
Eh?
咦
Are you all right, ma'am?
婆婆 妳怎麼了
My back hurts a bit
我的腰有點痛
so I sat down to rest.
只是稍微休息一下而已
Where do you live? I can carry you back.
妳家在哪裡 我背妳過去
It's okay. I live nearby.
不好啦 就在附近而已
Grab tight.
要抓好我喔
Let's go!
衝啊
Thank you.
謝謝妳啊
You're welcome.
不用客氣
Goodbye.
那我走了
All right.
好
Let's do this.
北部玄駒 要衝刺了
Eh?
咦
How are you?
你好嗎
Do you know where Tokyo Racecourse is?
請問東京競馬場在哪裡呢
Pardon. I can't speak English.
抱歉 我不會說英文
"TOKYO RACECOURSE" This one.
(東京競馬場) 就是這裡
Okay. Okay.
OK…
"CURRENT LOCATION" This!
(現在位置) 這裡
"HERE" This is very detailed.
(這裡) 簡單明瞭
Good luck!
祝你好運
Done.
好
I should head back to Tracen Academy now.
差不多該回去特雷森學園了…
A punctured tire!
爆胎了
You can run so fast.
好…好快
Thank you, Kita.
太感謝妳了 小北
Don't mention it.
完全不用客氣
It helps with my training too.
這也是很好的鍊習
Thank you so much.
謝謝妳了
You're welcome.
不會…
Dad taught me to help others,
爸爸常說 "見人有難就要馬上相助"
to cheer others,
"遇人失意就要一起歡笑"
and to put a smile on everyone's face.
"如此大家就都能常保笑容"
You're so kind, Kita.
真不愧是小北
Ever so helpful.
助人大將
You are a great help.
妳是助人大將呢
I know, right? Your presence always cheers everyone up.
就是啊 只要有小北在 大家就開朗了起來呢
Thank you, great helper!
助人大將…
By the way, what is the time now?
話說回來 現在是幾點呢
Morning.
早安
What's taking Kita so long?
小北好慢喔
Sheesh.
真是的
Diamond!
光鑽
I'm so sorry.
抱歉 光鑽
You shouldn't push yourself too far.
真是的 不可以勉強自己啦
You just completed a race.
而且妳才剛比賽完呢
Right.
是啊
Come, Kita.
快走吧 小北
Okay.
好
What is the first period?
第一節課是什麼啊
Home economics.
是家政課喔
Urgh, that scary teacher again.
那個可怕的老師嗎
This first…
先這樣…
"HOMEMAKING ROOM"
(被服室)
Then this…
再這樣…
Ow!
好痛
Are you all right?
妳沒事吧 小北
Show me your finger, Kita.
小北 手伸出來
Thanks a lot, Diamond.
謝謝妳 光鑽
You have to be careful with needles.
用針的時候要小心一點才行啊
"DERBY" I couldn't stop thinking about the race.
(德比) 心裡一直在想德比的事
It's around the corner.
終於就要到了呢 德比
If only I could debut together with you.
我也好想跟小北同一年出道喔
Diamond…
光鑽…
Have you always been good at embroidering?
光鑽妳以前就很擅長刺繡嗎
Not at all.
沒有
I merely follow the teacher's instructions.
是照著老師的示範做的
As expected from you then.
真不愧是光鑽
You're a fast learner.
不管什麼都學得很快呢
I am so clumsy compared to you.
跟妳相比 我從小就笨手笨腳的
DERBY
(德比)
"JAPANESE DERBY" Answer this question.
(日本德比) 那麼向大家提問
190,000 audiences cheered as Ines Fujin won the Derby.
在19萬人的歡呼中 贏下德比的是艾尼風神
The next one who won…
那麼接下來贏下德比的是…
-I know the answer. -Yes, Kitasan Black?
-我知道 -北部玄駒同學
It's Tokai Teio.
是東海帝皇
Exactly.
就是東海帝皇
The one who won the Derby before Mihono Bourbon…
那麼在美浦波旁之前 贏下德比的是…
It's Tokai Teio.
我知道 是東海帝皇
Yes.
就是東海帝皇
Kita, you're on fire today.
小北今天狀況也很好呢
Let's train together.
好了 來練習吧
You're even more excited after school.
但放學後才是精神最好的時候呢
Because I get to see Teio in person.
因為訓練時可以見到帝皇啊
If only you were on my team.
要是光鑽 也來我們的隊伍就更好了
Sorry that I went to another team…
抱歉 我進了別的隊伍了
For the Satono family, that team holds a special meaning.
對里見來說 那個隊伍是很特別的
The trainers and other athletes of Team Capella
Team Capella的訓練師 還有其他女孩
are all fighting for their dreams.
大家都是為了里見家的夢想在奮戰
We all share a common goal.
是個為此而生的隊伍
Here you are, Kita.
找到妳了 小北
Yes, yes.
對 沒錯 就是這樣
It is I, the come-and-go,
呼之則來的就是我 櫻花驀進王
"SAKURA BAKUSHIN O" Sakura Bakushin O.
(櫻花驀進王)
See you later, Kita.
那我就先走了喔 小北
Diamond, wait for me!
光…光鑽 等等我…
After your debut,
從出道到現在
I can tell that there's something special to your gait.
我在妳的跑勢上感覺到某種東西
That's right. I can feel the dormant,
沒錯 就沉睡在妳體內的爆進之力
explosive power inside you.
讓我猛烈地感受到了
I think you're perfect for a sprint.
依我之見 妳是適合短距離比賽的人
So let's rise to the top of sprinting.
來 跟我一起邁向短跑的極致吧
Come.
來吧…
Uhm…
那個…
I'm in Spica now.
我已經加入Spica了…
Sorry.
對不起
Why?
為…為什麼
Sigh.
真是的
I know she means well.
她並不是位壞學姐啊
She is quite nice, but…
她是位好學姐啊
As usual, you're the first, Kita.
今天也是小北第一個到呢
Special! Suzuka!
是小週還有鈴鹿
"SPECIAL WEEK, SILENCE SUZUKA"
(特別週 無聲鈴鹿)
Hello.
妳們好
Thank you for cleaning up the place, Kita.
謝謝妳總是幫忙打掃 小北
Don't mention it.
不會 不用客氣
Here. Thanks for tidying up.
接著 謝謝妳幫忙打掃
"DAIWA SCARLET, VODKA" Thanks.
(大和赤驥 伏特加) 謝謝妳
It was a gift, anyway.
別在意 反正也是別人送的
You bought it just now.
妳剛剛不是還特地去買嗎
We agreed not to tell her!
我不是說別講出來嗎
Move aside.
讓開…
"GOLD SHIP"
(黃金船)
I'm ready to fight Takarazuka Kinen…
做好面對寶塚紀念的黃金船來了…
All right. I'm done.
好 打掃完成
TEIO'S RACE
(帝皇的比賽)
JAPANESE DERBY, TOKYO RACECOURSE 2,400M LAP
(日本德比 東京競馬場) (草地 2400公尺)
You're watching it again.
妳又在看了啊
Don't you get sick of it, watching it every day?
每天看真虧妳不會膩呢
It's good to do some research.
用心鑽研是好事啊
I highly doubt she's researching.
但是她恐怕不只是在研究吧
She looks so awesome.
不論何時看都很帥呢
She breezed through her rivals,
像風一般飛馳而過
blitzed through her enemies.
像閃電一般轉瞬即逝
Please do this when I'm not here.
這種事我希望 妳能在本人不在的時候再做呢
Teio!
帝皇
You never change at all.
真是的 每天都這樣
"TOKAI TEIO, MEJIRO MCQUEEN"
(東海帝皇 目白麥昆)
Are you blushing?
妳在害羞嗎
Not at all.
才沒有呢
Uhm, Teio.
那…那個 帝皇
When you competed in the Derby,
妳在德比的時候…
what went on in your mind before the race?
在開賽前都在想些什麼呢
Hmm.
這個嘛
I thought about the winner's interview.
在想WINNING LIVE的事吧
She was already thinking about the things to do after the victory.
也就是說 她在想著贏下比賽之後的事
I—I see…
這…這樣啊
Woah.
好厲害…
Also, I thought about proving my worth to Rudolf.
還有就是想要表現給會長看
What about you, Special?
小週呢
I could only think about charging in.
我是想著要"咻"地一下衝出去吧
You're all here.
看來全都到了呢
Get changed and gather by the track.
換好衣服後就來跑道集合吧
Don't be late.
可別遲到了
Listen up, Kita.
聽好了 小北
The track in this Derby is 400 meters longer than the track in Satsuki Sho.
德比的賽程 比皐月賞多了400公尺
The straights in Fuchu are long,
而且府中的直線很長
which are not great for runners of your type.
對妳的腳質來說很是不利
You'll meet runners who save up a burst like Crown or Duramente.
畢竟有像里見皇冠還有大鳴大放 那種在最後大力衝刺的人在
However, it's too risky to change your gait now,
話雖如此 但改變腳質的風險太大
so you will play it to your advantage.
所以我們要強化妳的優勢
You'll focus on your stamina, and then, your endurance.
首要是體力 其次是持久力
Run at your own pace.
要練習到能跑出自己的節奏
Do not be distracted by your rivals.
無論對手怎麼跑都要不被其所惑
"DURAMENTE"
(大鳴大放)
Let's give it a try first.
首先 就先來跑一跑 習慣一下吧
Yes!
是…
Go!
衝啊
Kita is very motivated.
小北很有幹勁呢
Indeed.
是
Charge!
衝啊
Kitasan Black.
北部玄駒
Crown.
皇冠
"SATONO CROWN"
(里見皇冠)
Do you think you can win the Derby?
如何 能贏下德比嗎
I will.
當然 我會贏的
I have to.
這次一定要贏下來
The angle I took in Satsuki Sho put me at a disadvantage.
皐月賞時 因為斜行的關係有些不利
I have to improve myself before I win the race.
但只要變強就能贏下
Yeah.
是啊
I will win the first G1
里見家的首次GI勝利
for our family.
我定會將其拿下
If this carries on…
再這樣下去…
UMA MUSUME PRETTY DERBY SEASON 3
《賽馬娘 Pretty Derby 第三季》
DERBY
(德比)
Derby…
德比…
A once-in-a-lifetime stage.
一生只有一次的大舞台
The same tournament Teio took part in.
跟帝皇同樣的殊榮
I have to…
所以…我一定要…
Tomorrow is the day. Who do you think will win?
終於就是明天了 這次的德比 你怎麼看
Duramente, I think.
果然還是大鳴大放吧
She is very strong.
那種贏法真的很厲害
Some might even say she's a prodigy.
讓人覺得她真的是天才呢
You may cross now.
現在燈號是綠燈
Satono Crown might win too.
里見皇冠會不會後來居上啊
She is promising.
她的能力也很被人看好呢
What about Kitasan Black?
北部玄駒呢
She was very close last time.
上次太可惜了
But the track there is too long for her.
但這次對她來說 距離是不是太長了
Kita.
小北
Diamond, are you going back now?
光鑽 妳現在要回去嗎
Yes. You train very hard every day.
是啊 小北每天都很努力呢
Because Derby is around the corner.
因為德比就快要到了
I'll get changed now. Give me a minute.
我換個衣服就出來 妳等我一下喔
Okay.
好
As you can see here,
各位請看
the streets of Fuchu are teeming with people
在明天就要開始的日本德比前夜
on the eve of the Japanese Derby.
府中的街頭已經熱鬧滾滾了
Everyone is excited.
大家都是迫不急待的表情呢
-I can't wait. -Yeah.
-迫不急待呢 -是啊
I can't wait.
迫不急待了呢
Yummy.
好喝
Diamond.
那個…光鑽
How is Crown doing?
皇冠的狀況如何
She's quite relaxed
她還滿放鬆的
and she told me that she was in great form.
還跟我說狀況很完美呢
I see.
這樣啊
It's unusual of you to ask about others.
很難得呢 小北居然會去問其他人的事情
Oh.
是啊…
If you were racing in the Derby tomorrow,
我問妳 要是妳明天就要出賽德比的話
what do you think you'd think about when you're running?
妳在奔跑時會想些什麼呢
Winning the race.
想著勝利
That's all.
就只想著這一點
My family's curse will not be broken
要是沒有這種強烈決心
unless I have a firm resolution.
是無法打破里見的詛咒的
No one can predict the outcome,
沒人知道結果會如何
but…
但是我認為…
But you will definitely lose if you don't have faith in yourself.
要是對自己沒信心 是絕對無法贏下比賽的
Don't you agree, Kita?
小北不是這樣想嗎
I…
我…
G1 is still new to me.
GI是我從未經歷過的賽事
I'm seeing so many new things.
也是我未曾見過的景色
And the Derby is…
德比的話…
It's going to be more overwhelming.
應該就會更加的…
I can't be as confident as everyone.
我無法像大家一樣有自信
I see.
這樣啊
So you are afraid of the race.
小北妳在害怕德比呢
I think so, yeah.
好像是
No matter how hard I train, I feel like I don't stand a chance.
不管我怎麼練習 我都不覺得我能贏下比賽
I'm scared.
很害怕
Let me interview the public.
讓我們來聽聽大家的說法吧
The Japanese Derby is tomorrow.
明天終於就是日本德比了呢
Yes, my kid is looking forward to it.
是啊 我家小孩也很期待呢
Yes!
是啊
It's like a festival!
因為就像是祭典一樣啊
It's like a festival.
就像祭典一樣啊
She's such a cute girl, Kita.
那個女孩很可愛呢 小北
Kita?
小北…
Festival…
祭典…
-It is a festival. -Yes.
-是祭典呢 -是啊
It is a festival.
是祭典呢…
I…
那個…
The energetic, cheerful,
很有精神 很開朗
the one who puts a smile on everyone's faces…
能夠讓大家展露笑容的我 最喜歡的…
For me, Derby is…
那個德比是…
Kita?
小北
Diamond.
光鑽
I think I can do it.
我或許可以一拼了
I'll go and get some taiyaki.
我去買鯛魚燒
Yes, I'll be fine.
沒錯 一定沒問題的
Derby is just a festival.
德比就像是個開心又熱鬧的祭典
And I love festivals.
是我知道的景色
So, I…
這樣的話 我…
"SPECIAL TAIYAKI" Two taiyakis, please.
(特製鯛魚燒) 我要兩個鯛魚燒
Custard and…
口味要卡士德…
"SPECIAL TAIYAKI" Custard for both.
(特製鯛魚燒) 不 要卡士達醬
The Japanese Derby will begin soon.
好了 日本德比終於要開始了
How will the horse girls perform? What will happen?
今年會出現什麼樣的賽馬娘 會用什麼樣跑法 跑出什麼樣的比賽
We are all waiting for the answers.
將其深深烙印在我們的心中呢
Mr. Yamamoto.
山本先生
Pleased to work with you today.
今天也請您多多指教了
Likewise.
好的 請多指教
Winning this race
取得德比桂冠這個殊榮
means you are the fastest and the No. 1 horse girl in the world.
就代表她成為該世代最強 亦是NO.1的證明
They will do their best to bring us a thrilling race.
希望她們窮盡所有力量 完成一場出色的比賽
This is Derby.
我要出賽德比了
I will run happily, joyfully.
要跑得開心 跑得快樂
I will be my true self.
跑出自我
Remember, your pacing is very important.
聽好了 重點是步調
Don't be intimidated by the atmosphere or your rivals.
別被氣氛還有對手壓倒了
All the best.
妳要加油
Kita, you have this.
沒問題的 小北一定會贏的
Enjoy the nervousness too.
去享受所有的不安和緊張吧
Kita.
小北
Be yourself, okay?
要跑出自我 知道嗎
Yes!
是
Here she is, the highly-anticipated horse girl.
好了 眾所矚目的就是這位賽馬娘
"DURAMENTE, PREVIOUSLY ON SATSUKI SHO" She won Satsuki Sho
(大鳴大放 前次比賽 皐月賞) 以壓倒性的實力
with her overwhelming speed.
贏下皐月賞的大鳴大放
"DURAMENTE, PREVIOUSLY ON SATSUKI SHO" I hope she can get the triple crown.
(大鳴大放 前次比賽 皐月賞) 期待她能奪得三冠
She showed us the burst she is capable of in Nakayama.
在中山讓我們見識到 那可怕的最後加速
In this long, straight running track,
在這有長直線的府中賽場
will we witness her burst again?
會再度爆發出來嗎
"SATONO CROWN, PREVIOUSLY ON SATSUKI SHO" Next, Satono Crown.
(里見皇冠 前次比賽 皐月賞) 接下來是里見皇冠
On her quest to winning G1,
背負著贏得GI夙願的她
"SATONO CROWN, PREVIOUSLY ON SATSUKI SHO" what will she show us today?
(里見皇冠 前次比賽 皐月賞) 會讓我們見識到什麼樣的比賽呢
Her previous score does not put her in an advantageous position
從之前的成績來看對她有點不利
but if she finds her rhythm here,
但要是她能跑出本來的步調的話
she can and will win this race.
也是很有機會贏下這場比賽的
I can't lose. I must win.
我不能輸 只能贏
I
那種詛咒
will break this curse.
我一定會打破它的
Here, the 3rd place in Satsuki Sho,
接下來是皐月賞第三名
Kitasan Black.
北部玄駒
I heard she trained very hard for this race.
聽說她為了這次比賽 做了不少訓練
She does not look fatigued though.
從外表上看起來並沒有疲憊的樣子
She looks motivated.
看起來精神奕奕
I can't wait for her performance.
期待她的表現
That was where I cheered for Teio.
那是我那個時候 看著帝皇飛奔而過的加油席
All right then.
好
G1, JAPANESE DERBY, TOKYO YUSHUN TOKYO RACECOURSE, 2,400M COURSE
(GI 日本德比 東京優駿) (東京競馬場 草地2400公尺)
The biggest race that decides the champion of horse girls,
決定世代頂點的閃光系列賽 其中的最大比賽
Tokyo Yushun, Japanese Derby.
東京優駿 日本德比
18 horse girls, each carrying a dream
心中懷抱各自的夢想
on their shoulders
這被選上的18位賽馬娘
enter the starting gate.
緩緩地進入閘門了
Everything is in position now.
好了 全都準備完成了
May destiny lead them to their glory.
已盡人事 等待榮耀降臨
No, they will earn glory with sheer will!
不 要用執念來抓住勝利
Start!
起跑了
6 had a later start,
雖然6號直擊子彈起步稍晚
but everyone was off to a great start.
但各賽馬娘的起步都相當漂亮
Which one of them will reach the spectator's stand first?
是哪位賽馬娘會先衝過看台呢
-Go! -Will it be
-衝啊… -會是最外側的美技進球衝出來嗎
America Spike?
會是最外側的美技進球衝出來嗎
Kitasan Black approached the middle now.
北部玄駒也衝上前了 她往中間靠了
Ribbon Pia is in the lead,
現在是緞帶凱歌領先
but how long can she maintain it?
她會持續領先下去嗎
Kitasan Black is following closely behind.
北部玄駒就緊追在後
The cheering is loud.
好大的歡呼聲
As if it could crush me.
聲音化為實體朝我衝來
But…
但是
We're now heading to the most difficult part, the first bend.
好了 進入困難重重的 第一彎道的中間地帶了
The luckiest one will always win the Derby.
運氣最強的賽馬娘會贏下德比
Such as Eishin Flash, Tanino Gimlet, and Special Week.
像是榮進閃耀 谷水琴蕾 還有特別週
Records show it's usually won by the third place of Satsuki Sho.
從資料上來看 很多都是 皐月賞第三名的賽馬娘贏下的
Why is that?
為什麼突然說這個
Do you know who is the third place in this year's Satsuki Sho?
你知道今年的皐月賞第三名是誰嗎
That's right. It's Kitasan Black.
沒錯 就是北部玄駒
I see.
那就沒問題了
After the difficult second bend, they have arrived at the straight.
過了困難的第二彎道 來到非終點直道
Let's see who has the lead.
好了 從領先的賽馬娘來看吧
Ribbon Pia is first,
領先的是緞帶凱歌
followed by Kitasan Black.
接著是北部玄駒
Duramente is in the middle.
大鳴大放位在中段
Can Satono Crown redeem herself here?
里見皇冠能夠 一雪皐月賞時的恥辱嗎
It says 58.8 seconds when they crossed the 1,000-meter mark.
通過1000公尺處時 顯示為58秒8
Too fast.
是不是有點太快了
Kita got carried away.
是不是有點太投入了 北部
The sun is glaring in the Tokyo Racecourse.
炙熱的陽光照射著這裡 府中東京競馬的草地
She's the only one ahead of me.
在我前面的只有她一個人
I can see the finishing line now.
已經看到終點了
We are now at the fourth bend.
來了第四彎道了
After this is the final stretch.
過了這裡之後 就是無法回頭的決一死戰
Everything is at stake.
賭上一切…
-I can do this. -Everything is at stake.
-可以的 -賭上一切…
-From here to the finishing line… -The final stretch of this race.
-但是從這裡的話… -這是日本德比的最後直線了
-I have to win.
-要贏
-I must win. -Go.
-我一定要贏 -全力追上去
Kitasan Black and Ribbon are going neck and neck.
北部玄駒跟首位並排了
Go!
衝啊…
Ribbon will not concede either.
第一名也不遑多讓
I'm so close. So close.
還差一點…
They won't give up that easily.
不相上下 緞帶凱歌
Kitasan Black is still chasing.
北部玄駒也緊追不捨
Will one of them win this race?
會是領先的這些賽馬娘 決定比賽的勝負嗎
But it's too early to say.
但勝負還在未定之天
This long final stretch
漫長的府中最後直線
is their one-way ticket to glory.
這條通向榮耀的單行道
18 horse girls are giving their all.
18位賽娘同時一起衝了上去
Here she is.
就在這個時候
Duramente accelerated.
她來了 大鳴大放來了
I won't lose. The fight is just starting!
不能輸 勝負才要開始呢
The final 200 meters!
剩下 200公尺
Duramente is in the lead.
大鳴大放領先
No. The finishing line is not here yet.
還沒 終點還沒到
She is so fast.
果然很強
She overtook everyone.
一瞬間就超越過去了
Duramente got two crowns!
大鳴大放 完成二冠殊榮
No one can stop her!
簡直是無人能擋
She overtook everyone in seconds!
一瞬間就超越過去了
Incredible!
太強了
Duramente has obtained two of the three crowns!
在新時代的日本德比中 大鳴大放完成二冠殊榮
Yes!
好啊
What is her ranking?
她第幾名
I think…
我想應該是…
14th.
第14名
If I'm not mistaken.
要是我沒看錯的話
2 minutes 23.2 seconds.
2分23秒2
That is the record for this year's Derby.
這是這次德比的紀錄
Without a doubt, it's a landslide victory!
是個無話可說的壓倒性勝利
Please cheer for Duramente!
請給大鳴大放掌聲鼓勵
I lost…
我輸掉了…